<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TwoActivitiesChallange</string>
    <string name="button1">Paragraph 1</string>
    <string name="button2">Paragraph 2</string>
    <string name="button3">Paragraph 3</string>

    <string name="displayText_one">Accounting is one of the key functions of almost any business.
        It may be handled by a bookkeeper or an accountant at a small firm, or by sizable finance
        departments with dozens of employees at larger companies. The reports generated by various
        streams of accounting, such as cost accounting and managerial accounting, are invaluable in
        helping management make informed business decisions. </string>

    <string name="displayText_two">The manga spawned a media franchise, having been adapted into a festival
        film produced by Production I.G, and an anime series produced by Toei Animation, which began
        broadcasting in Japan in 1999. Additionally, Toei has developed fourteen animated feature films,
        one OVA and thirteen television specials. Several companies have developed various types of
        merchandising and media, such as a trading card game and numerous video games. The manga series
        was licensed for an English language release in North America and the United Kingdom by Viz
        Media and in Australia by Madman Entertainment. The anime series was licensed by 4Kids Entertainment
        for an English-language release in North America in 2004, before the license was dropped and
        subsequently acquired by Funimation in 2007.</string>

    <string name="displayText_three">At a drama set Dal-gun watches a report of a plane crash that
        killed over 200 civilians due to structural failure. He is completely shocked when he realizes
        that it is the exact same plane his nephew had taken to Morocco. With his world now turned upside down,
        Dal-gun travels to Morocco to attend the funeral for all the victims of the plane crash, grieving for
        the loss of his nephew.Dal-gun is about to return home, when he recognizes a supposedly dead passenger
        from the video his nephew had recorded.[9] He manages to confront the man and slowly begins to realize
        that the plane crash was not caused by a malfunction. However, any evidence he finds is mysteriously
        erased and his life is threatened whenever he tries to prove to others that the plane crash was not an
        accident.</string>
</resources>